---------------------------------------------------------------------------------
  Changelog for "Rainbeau's Rumor Has It...."
---------------------------------------------------------------------------------

- 11/03/2018
	- Added the "Quarrel" incident. (This was taken from Linq/World-Mule's
	  "Expanded Incidents" mod.)
	- The negative impact of the Annoying Voice, Creepy Breathing, Disfigured,
	  and Ugly traits is now reduced for pawns who have any of those traits 
	  themselves. (This was originally a feature in SeveralPuffins' "Romance 
	  Diversified," but it didn't make it into "Rational Romance," as I think it
	  fits better here, in a mod that primarily focuses on what pawns think of
	  each other.)
	- Made some slight adjustments to the mod's mood penalties and buffs, making
	  them generally a bit milder. They still won't seem unreasonably low when
	  compared to vanilla penalties and buffs, but also shouldn't seem too high
	  when matched against those of "Grim Reality" or similar mods.

- 11/01/2018
	- Initial release of "Rumor Has It" for RimWorld 1.0.

- 06/13/2017
    - SeveralPuffins' final update to his mod.
	
- 05/29/2017
    - Updated for alpha 17.

- 12/21/2016
    - Updated for alpha 16.
	
- 11/06/2016
    - Initial release of SeveralPuffins' "Rumours and Deception" for RimWorld
	  alpha 15.
	  